A Finding Aid to the Cranmer Art Group Records, circa 1980-2021, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Materials, circa 1980-2008; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 19 Linear feet Boxes 55-74
  - Slides, 2002, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 15-16)
  - Slides, 2002, G-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Slides, 2002, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Slides, 2002, K-L, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Slides, 2002, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 20-21)
  - Slides, 2002, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 22-26)
  - Slides, 2002, N-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 2002, P-Q, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 2002, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 3-4)
  - Slides, 2002, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 5-6)
  - Slides, 2002, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Slides, 2002, V-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Slides, 2002, W-Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Slides, 2003, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 10-11)
  - Slides, 2003, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Slides, 2003, B-C, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Slides, 2003, C-D, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Slides, 2003, D-E, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Slides, 2003, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Slides, 2003, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Slides, 2003, G-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Slides, 2003, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 19-20)
  - Slides, 2003, H-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Slides, 2003, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Slides, 2003, K-L, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Slides, 2003, L-M, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Slides, 2003, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 25-26)
  - Slides, 2003, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 1-7)
  - Slides, 2003, N, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Slides, 2003, N-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Slides, 2003, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Slides, 2003, P-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Slides, 2003, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 12-13)
  - Slides, 2003, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Slides, 2003, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Slides, 2003, S-T, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Slides, 2003, T-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Slides, 2003, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Slides, 2003, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Slides, 2004, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 20-21)
  - Slides, 2004, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 22-23)
  - Slides, 2004, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Slides, 2004, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Slides, 2004, D-E, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Slides, 2004, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Slides, 2004, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 2004, F-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 2004, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 3-4)
  - Slides, 2004, G-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Slides, 2004, H-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Slides, 2004, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Slides, 2004, K-L, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Slides, 2004, L-M, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Slides, 2004, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 10-13)
  - Slides, 2004, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Slides, 2004, O-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Slides, 2004, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Slides, 2004, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 17-18)
  - Slides, 2004, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Slides, 2004, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 20-22)
  - Slides, 2004, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Slides, 2004, V-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Slides, 2004, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Slides, 2005, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 26-27)
  - Slides, 2005, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Slides, 2005, B-C, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 2005, C-D, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 2005, D-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Slides, 2005, F-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Slides, 2005, G-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Slides, 2005, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Slides, 2005, H-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Slides, 2005, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 8-9)
  - Slides, 2005, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 10-11)
  - Slides, 2005, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 12-15)
  - Slides, 2005, N-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Slides, 2005, P-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Slides, 2005, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 18-19)
  - Slides, 2005, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Slides, 2005, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Slides, 2005, S-T, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Slides, 2005, T-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Slides, 2005, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Slides, 2006, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Slides, 2006, A-C, Archival Resource Key (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Slides, 2006, C-D, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 2006, D-E, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 2006, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Slides, 2006, F-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Slides, 2006, G-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Slides, 2006, H-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Slides, 2006, K-L, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Slides, 2006, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Slides, 2006, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 9-11)
  - Slides, 2006, M-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Slides, 2006, O-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Slides, 2006, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 14-15)
  - Slides, 2006, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Slides, 2006, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Slides, 2006, T-U, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Slides, 2006, V-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Slides, 2006, W-Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, B-C, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, D-E, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, F-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 5-7)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, H-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 11-12)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, M-N, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, O-Q, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 15-16)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, S-T, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, T-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Slides, 2007-2008, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 74, Folder 22)